Guide to the Yale Divinity School Faculty Writings and Publications
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Faculty A-L
  - Hare, John E.
    - Kant and Depravity. Philosophia Christi, v.9, no.1, 2007, pp.21-27. (Box 12)
    - Kant and the Rational Instability of Atheism. in God and the Ethics of Belief: New Essays in Philosophy of Religion, ed. Andrew Dole and Andrew Chignell, Cambridge: 2006. (Box 12)
    - Kant on Recognizing our Duties as God's Commands. Faith and Philosophy, v.17, no.4, Oct. 2000, pp.459-478. (Box 12)
    - Kant on Recognizing our Duties as God's Commands. in Philosophy of Religion, ed. Melville Y. Stewart and Xing Taotao, pp.513-529. (Box 12)
    - Kant's Divine Command Theory and its Reception within Analytic Philosophy. in Kant and Kierkegaard on Religion, ed. D.Z. Phillips and Timothy Tessin. Claremont Studies in the Philosophy of Religion, 2000, pp.263-277. (Box 12)
    - Kantian Ethics, International Politics, and the Enlargement of the Foedus Pacificum. in Sovereignty at the Crossroads? Morality and International Politics in the Post-Cold War Era. 1996, pp.71-92. (Box 12)
    - Kantian Moral Education and Service-Learning. in Commitment and Connection: Service Learning and Christian Higher Education, ed. Gail Heffner and Claudia Beversluis. Lanham: University Press of America, 2002, pp.73-95. (Box 12)
    - The Limits of Paternalism in Emergency Care. Hastings Center Report, with John Clarke and John Sorenson, December 1980, pp. 120-122. (Box 12)
    - Moral Misdeeds: What's Private? What's Public? The Banner, Sept. 13, 1999. (Box 12)
    - Moral Motivation. in Games, Groups, and the Global Good, ed. Simon A. Levin, 2009, pp.181-193. (Box 12)
    - Morality and God. Center for the Study of Ethics in Society, v.13, no.2, Feb. 2001, 26 pgs. (Box 12)
    - Il Movimento Hospice e l'Accettazione Della Morte. tr. Luca Marmiroli. Progressi Clinici: Medicina, v. 3, no. 3, 1988, pp. 137-140. (Box 12)
    - Naturalism and Morality. in Naturalism: A Critical Analysis, ed. William Lane Craig and J.P. Moreland. London: Routledge, 2000, pp.189-211 (Box 12)
    - Nuclear Deterrence as Bluff: A Dialogue on the Moral Costs. with J. Ralph Lindgren. in Political Realism and International Morality: Ethics in the Nuclear Age, Westview Press, 1987, pp.144-152. (Box 12)
    - On Recognizing our Duties as God's Commands. Moralische Motivation: Kant und die Alternativen. 2006, pp.275-285. (Box 12)
    - Philosophy in the Legislative Process. The International Journal of Applied Philosophy, v. 2, no. 2, Fall 1984, pp. 81- 88. (Box 12)
    - Plato's Euthyphro. Bryn Mawr Commentaries, 1981. (Box 12)
    - Politics and Salt. Relfections, Yale Divinity School: Fall 2004, pp. 21-24. (Box 12)
    - Prescriptive Realism. Philosophia Reformata, v.71, no.1, 2006, pp.14-30 (Box 12)
    - Prescriptive Realism. in Realism and Religion: Philosophical and Theological Perspectives, Ashgate: 2007. (Box 12)
    - Puffing up the Capacities. Journal of Philosophical Research, v.19, 1994, pp.77-88. (Box 12)
    - R.M. Hare: A Memorial Address. Utilitas, v.14, no.3, Nov. 2002, pp.306-308. (Box 12)
    - Scotus on Morality and Nature. Medieval Philosophy and Theology, v.9, 2000, pp.15-38. (Box 12)
    - The Supervenience of Goodness on Being. in Metaphysics and God: Essays in Honor of Eleonore Stump, ed. Kevin Timpe. New York: Routledge, 2009, pp.143-156. (Box 12)
    - Thorns [Poem]. Prospect, v.2, Spring 2007, p.6. (Box 12)
    - Too Far the Pendulum Swings: Response to Hendrik Hart. inAn Ethos of Campassion and the Intergrity of Creation. Lanham: University Press of America, 1995, pp.102-108. (Box 12)
    - The Unhappiest One and the Structure of Kierkegaard's Either/Or. International Kierkegaard Commentary, v.3, ed. Robert L. Perkins, 1995. (Box 12)
    - The Virtue of Hope. in Heaven and Hell, Christian Reflection: A Series in Faith and Ethics, Baylor, 2002. (Box 12)
    - Why Betrand Russell was not a Christian. Books and Culture: A Christian Review, May/June 1997, pp.26-28. (Box 12)
    - Book Reviews
      - Christian Faith, Health, and Medical Practice. Perspectives, November 1991, pp. 20-22. (Box 12)
      - Creating the Kingdom of Ends, by Christine Korsgaard. Faith and Philosophy, v.17, no.3, July 2000, pp.371-383. (Box 12)
      - An Essay on Divine Authority, by Mark Murphy. Mind, v.113, no.450, April 2004, pp.375-379. (Box 12)
      - Just War and the Gulf War, by James Turner Johnson and George Weigel. Calvin Theological Journal, v.28, no.2, November 1993, pp. 473-476. (Box 12)
      - Kant on God, by Peter Byrne. Religion Theology, v.7, no.1, May 2009, pp.71-83 (Box 12)
      - Kant's Philosophy of Religion Reconsidered, by Philip J. Rossi and Michael Wreen. Faith and Philosophy, v.11, no.1, Jan. 1994, pp.138-144. (Box 12)
      - Kierkegaard and the Limits of the Ethical, by Anthony Rudd. Studies in Christian Ethics, v.8, no.1, 1995, pp.138-143. (Box 12)
      - Law, Morality, and the Relations of States, by Terry Nardin. Philosophical Books, v.25, no.4, Oct. 1984, pp.240-241. (Box 12)
      - Line in the Sand: Justice and the Gulf War, by Alan Geyer and Barbara Green. Calvin Theological Journal, v.27, no.2, Nov. 1992, pp.483-486. (Box 12)
      - The Moral Interpretation of Religion, by Peter Byrne. Studies in Christian Ethics, v.12, no.2, 1999, pp.74-78. (Box 12)
  - Harris, Samuel
  - Hartt, Julian
    - A Christian View of Freedom. YDS Religion at the News Desk program: Feb. 23, 1952. (Box 11)
    - Dialectic, Analysis and Empirical Generalization in Theology. Crozer Quarterly: Jan, 1952, pp. 1-17. (Box 11)
    - Liturgy and Politics. From The Church, The University and Social Policy, Vol. 2, 20 pp. (Box 11)
    - The Problem of Symbolic Adequacy in Protestantism, Dec. 19, 1963, 6 pages. (Box 11)
    - Seminar in Contemporary Theology (Existentialism) Fall term 1950-1951. Typescript pp. 1-61. (Box 11)
  - Hawkins, Peter S.
    - A Prophetic Call to Judgement. pp. 1-8., n.d. (Box 11)
    - 'By Gradual Scale Sublimed' Dante's Benedict and Contemplative Ascent. Dante Semician, pp.255-269. (Box 11)
    - Dante's Paradiso and the Dialectic of Ineffability. Ineffability: Naming the Unnamable from Dante to Beckett, New York, (1984), pp. 1-21. (Box 11)
    - Dido, Beatrice, and the Signs of Ancient Love. pp. 1-13 (Box 11)
    - Faith and Doubt First Class: The Letters of Flannery O'Connor. Southern Humanities Review, vol.16, No. 2, Spring 1982, pp. 1-13. (Box 11)
    - Getting Somewhere. pp. 104-133., n.d. (Box 11)
    - for Imagining Mortality. pp. 1-5., n.d. (Box 11)
    - 'Out Upon Circumference': Discovery in Dante. pp. 1-43. (Box 11)
    - Polemical Counterpoint in 'De Civitate Dei.' Augustine Studies, vol. 6, 1975, pp.97-106. (Box 11)
    - Resurrecting the Word: Dante and the Bible. Religion and Literature, vol. 16.3, Fall 1984, pp. 59-71. (Box 11)
    - Transfiguring the Text: Ovid, Scripture and the Dynamics of Allusion. Stamford Italian Studies, (1986) pp. 1-46. (Box 11)
    - Virtuosity and Virtue: Poetic Self-Reflection in the 'Commedia.' vol. 98, 1980, pp. 1-18. (Box 11)
  - Hayes, Richard B.
    - An Interpretive Paraphrase of 1 Cor. 7: 1-7. Feb. 18, 1982, 1 page. (Box 11)
    - Christology and Ethics in Galatians: The Law of Christ. Catholic Biblical Quarterly, v49, 1987, pp.268-290. (Box 11)
    - Do Not Cling to Me. Easter Sunday Sunrise Service, YDS, March 30, 1986, pp.1-2 (Box 11)
    - Effects of Inertextual Echo in Romans: Preliminary Soundings. 1985 SBL Meeting, Pauline Epistles Section, pp. 1-10. (Box 11)
    - "Have we found Abraham to be our forefather according to the flesh?", A Reconsideration of Rom. 4:1, Nov Test, XXVII/1, 1985, pp. 76-98. (Box 11)
    - Jesus' Faith and Ours: A Re-reading of Galatians 3. TSF Bulletin, Sept.-Oct. 1983, pp.2-6. (Box 11)
    - The Law of Christ:Christology and Ethics in Galatians. pp. 1- 49. (Box 11)
    - The Lord's Release Has Been Proclaimed. Downtown Cooperative Ministry, Thanksgiving Day Community Service. Center Church, New Haven, CT. Nov. 28, 1985, pp. 1-5. (Box 11)
    - Making the Love of God Visible. Wedding Sermon, July 21, 1984, pp. 1-5. (Box 11)
    - Paul as Reader and Misreader of Scripture: Retrospect and Prospects. For SBL New England Regional Meeting, March 22, 1985, pp.1-30. (Box 11)
    - Psalm 143 and the Logic of Romans 3, Journal of Biblical Literature, 99/1, 1980, pp. 107-115. (Box 11)
    - The Qumran Community. pp. 1-36., n.d. (Box 11)
    - Relations Natural and Unnatural: A Response to John Boswell's Exegesis of Romans 1. The Journal of Religious Ethics, pp. 184-215. (Box 11)
    - 'The Righteous One' as Eschatological Deliverer: A Case Study In Paul's Apocalyptic Hermeneutics. 36 pgs., n.d. (Box 11)
    - Testing the Water. Preached in Marquand Chapel, YDS, Feb. 22, 1988, pp. 1-4. (Box 11)
  - Hein, Jeanne
    - Father Henrique's Grammar of Spoken Tamil, 1548, Indian Church History Review: August, 1977, pp. 127-157. (Box 11)
    - Language Encounter in 16th Century Goa, Heras Institute of Indian History and Culture International Seminar on IndoPortuguese History, 16 pp. (Box 11)
  - Hein, Norvin
    - Articles
      - Caitanya's Ecstasies and the Theology of the Name. From Hinduism: New Essays in the History of Religions, Bardwell L. Smith, ed., 1976, pp. 15-32. (Box 11)
      - Christ's Hypocrites. Chapel Sermon Jan. 28, 1952. (Box 11)
      - Early Foreign Observers at the Ras Lila. Festschrift Poddar, 1953, pp. 713-717. (Box 11)
      - Early Protestant Views of Hinduism 1600-1825. (Box 11)
      - Hinduism. Article in American Oxford Encyclopedia (Box 11)
      - Jains. Article in American Oxford Encyclopedia, n.d. (Box 11)
      - Monotheism in the Bhagavadgita: A Stylistic Clue. Proceedings of the XII International Congress for the History of Religions, 1970. (Box 11)
      - The Ramcaritmanas in the life of Krsna Devotees. Boeings and Bullock-Carts: Studies in Change and Continuity in Indian Civilization. Bardwell L. Smith ed., Chanakya Publications: Delhi, 1990, pp. 27-37. (Box 11)
      - The Ramcaritmanas in Mathura. Conference on Tulsi Das organized by the Centre of South Asian Studies, March 1974, 19 pp. (Box 11)
      - The Ram Lila. Journal of American Folklore, Jul-Sep 1958, pp. 279-304. (Box 11)
      - The Test of Conflict. Chapel sermon, Jan. 29, 1952. (Box 11)
      - Foreword to Shri Vallabhacharya--His Philosophy and Religion, by Prof. Jethalal G. Shah. (Box 11)
      - Epic Sarvabhutahite Ratah: A Byword of Non-Bhargava Editors. Annals of the Bhandarkar Oriental Research Institute, Vol 67, 1986. (Box 11)
      - Lila (encyclopedia article), The Encyclopedia of Religion, ed. by Mircea Eliade (N.Y., Macmillian Publishing Co., 1987), Vol. 8. (Box 11)
      - A Revolution in Krsnaism: The Cult of Gopala. History of Religions, Vol. 25, No. 4, May 1986. (Box 11)
      - Kalayavana. From Mathura, Doris Meth Srinivasan, ed., 1989, pp. 223-235. (Box 11)
      - Introduction to the 39th session, 16th Annual Conference of South Asia, in Rediscovering Braj, Dec. 1988, pp. 9-13. (Box 11)
      - Norvin Hein Collection of Press Prints. Syracuse University Library, (Guide Sheet), 1 page., n.d. (Box 11)
      - Exhibitions in the Yale University Library on the occasion of the 170th meeting of the American Oriental Society. Yale University, Mar. 29-31, 1960. (Box 11)
      - Letter to Senator Chris Dodd on the topic of Muslim Immigration, 2008 (Box 11)
      - Those Tasty Pork Sausages on a Traditional Farm, for the Bethany Historical Society, presented to the New-Life Breakfast Club, June 11, 2008. 15 pages. (Box 11)
      - A Symbol in the Paintings of Josef Albers: Reflections sprung from a visit to the Josef Albers Foundation, Nov. 27, 2000. 26 pages. (Box 11)
      - Islamic Law on Holy War: An authoritative manual. Presentation at the United Church, Bethany, Nov. 11, 2001. 11 pages. (Box 11)
      - The Wedding of Indira Nehru. Feb. 17, 1999. 20 pages. (Box 11)
      - Wooster-in-India Men: How one got home, 1943, 27 pages. (Box 11)
      - War in Navarre: 1656, Jan. 14, 2008, 16 pages. (Box 11)
    - Book Reviews
      - Entwistle, A.W., Braj: Centre of Krishna Pilgrimage, Journal of the American Oriental Society, 109.3, 1989, pp. 466-468. (Box 11)
      - Haberman, D.L., Journey through the Twelve Forests, an Encounter with Krishna (1994) in Journal of Asian Studies, 54:3, Aug. 1995, pp. 875-877. (Box 11)
      - Lynch, O.M., Divine Passions: The Social Construction of Emotions in India (1990) in Journal of the American Oriental Society, 111:3, 1991, p. 592-593. (Box 11)
  - Hicks, R. Lansing
    - Articles
      - A Bibliography of James Muilenburg's Writings, in Israel's Prophetic Heritage, B. W. Anderson and W. Harrelson, eds., 1962, pp. 233-242. (Box 14)
      - Delet and Megillah: A Fresh Approach to Jeremiah XXXVI, Vetus Testamentum, XXXIII/1, 1983, pp. 46-66. (Box 14)
      - The Door of Love, Love & Death in the Ancient Near East: Essays in Honor of Marvin H. Pope, Four Quarters Pub. Co., 1987. (Box 14)
      - Form and Content: A Hermeneutical Application, in Translating and Understanding the Bible, 1970, pp. 304- 324. (Box 14)
      - Forms of Christ in the Old Testament. William C. Winslow Memorial Lectures, 1969, 45 pp. (Box 14)
      - G. Ernest Wright and Old Testament Theology, Anglican Theological Review, 58, 1976, pp. 158-178. (Box 14)
      - Jesus and His Church, Anglican Theological Review, 33, 1951, pp. 85-94. (Box 14)
      - The Jewish Background to the New Testament Doctrine of the Church, Anglican Theological Review, 30, 1948, pp. 107- 117. (Box 14)
      - Messiah, Second Moses, Son of Man, Anglican Theological Review, Vol. 33, 1951. (Box 14)
      - Present-Day Trends in Biblical Theology, Anglican Theological Review, 32, 1950, pp. 24-29. (Box 14)
      - Recent Old Testament Literature, Reflection, Jan 1979, pp. 12-14. (Box 14)
      - Research in the Old Testament (1947), Journal of Bible and Religion, Vol 17, 1949. (Box 14)
      - Walther Eichrodt's Theology of the Old Testament, Anglican Theological Review, 47, 1964, pp. 1-11. (Box 14)
      - Curriculum Vitae, n.d. (Box 14)
    - Book Reviews
      - Brueggemann, Walter, Tradition for Crisis: A Study in Hosea, Journal of Biblical Literature, 91, 1972, pp. 105-107. (Box 14)
      - van Imschoot, P., Theologie de l'Ancien Testament, Tome I, Dieu, Journal of Biblical Literature, 75/4, 1956, pp. 339-340. (Box 14)
  - Holmer, Paul L.
    See Record Group No. 195.
  - Huebner, Dwayne E.
    - Curriculum Vitae, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Robert Clyde
    - A Theologian of Synthesis. Theology Today, pp. 36-42., n.d. (Box 14)
    - The Church and Its Changing Ministry, Robert C. Johnson, ed.: Chapter 1 - "The Posture of the Church" (Box 14)
    - The Church and Its Changing Ministry, Robert C. Johnson, ed.: Chapter 2 - "The Ministry of Order" (Box 14)
    - The Church and Its Changing Ministry, Robert C. Johnson, ed.: Chapter 3 - "The Church's Ministry" (Box 14)
    - The Church and Its Changing Ministry, Robert C. Johnson, ed.: Chapter 5 - "The Reformation and the Ministry" (Box 14)
    - The Church and Its Changing Ministry, Robert C. Johnson, ed.: Chapter 12 - " The Doctrine of the Ministry" (Box 14)
    - The Church Celebrates, Counsel, 21/4, Jul-Sep 1969, pp. 38-41. (Box 14)
    - The Confessional Approach, Authority in Protestant Theology, pp. 162-188., n.d. (Box 14)
    - The Doctrine of the Ministry, Chapter 12 of The Church and Its Changing Ministry, Robt. C. Johnson, ed., pp. 97-106. (Box 14)
    - Faithful Audacity, Yale, n.d. (Box 14)
    - "Life and Death and Our Children", Opening Doors, 10/2, Jan-Mar 1958, pp. 13-15. (Box 14)
    - The Living Lord, a three-article study, Crossroads, 7/3, Apr-Jun, 1957, pp. 54-61.: At His Table (Box 14)
    - The Living Lord, a three-article study, Crossroads, 7/3, Apr-Jun, 1957, pp. 54-61.: Under His Cross (Box 14)
    - The Living Lord, a three-article study, Crossroads, 7/3, Apr-Jun, 1957, pp. 54-61.: Before His Tomb (Box 14)
    - The Ministry as Work, Theology Today, XVII/3, Oct 1960, pp. 275-282. (Box 14)
    - Our God is One Lord, Opening Doors, 13/2, Jan-Mar 1961, pp. 14-17. (Box 14)
    - Paul Tillich, Crossroads, 7/4, Jul-Sep, 1957, pp. 2-6. (Box 14)
    - Paul Tillich, Chapter VIII of Ten Makers of Modern Protestant Thought, Geo. L. Hunt, ed., 1958, pp. 89-101. (Box 14)
    - Paul Tillich, Chapter VI in Twelve Makers of Modern Protestant Thought, Geo. L. Hunt, ed., 1971, pp. 65-73. (Box 14)
    - The Problem of Doubt, Crossroads, 6/1, Oct-Dec, 1955, pp. 50-53. (Box 14)
    - "The Problem of Suffering", Crossroads, Vol. 6, No. 2, Jan-Mar 1956, pp. 79-81. (Box 14)
    - "Ray Wood and the Sixties: A Tribute", Reflections, Winter/Spring 1991, pp. 22-24. (Box 15)
    - The Reformation Rehabilitation of Ordination and the Ministry, Western Watch, May 1959, pp. 1-17. (Box 15)
    - "Robert C. Johnson Retires", Spectrum, No. 7, May 1990, pp. 4-6. (Box 15)
    - The Roman Church Revives, Counsel, 6/3, Apr-Jun 1954, pp.30-31. (Box 15)
    - The Scientific and Narrative Approaches, Authority in Protestant Theology, pp. 144-152. (Box 15)
    - Seeking the Kingdom, Crossroads, 4/4, Jul-Sep 1954, pp. 61-79. (Box 15)
    - "Symposium on Tillich's Theology: A Theologian of Synthesis", Theology Today, Vol. XV, No. 1, Apr 1958, pp. 36-42. (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: Jesus as Teacher (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: Jesus, Bearer of the Word (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: The Gospel of the Kingdom (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: The Kingdom and History (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: The Reinterpretation of Our Need (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: Jesus, Revealer of God (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: The Holy God of Jesus (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: Our Response to God's Gift (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: The Self-emptied Life (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: The Life of Forgiving Love (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: The "End" of Life (Box 15)
    - The Teaching of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 5/2, Jan 1955, pp. 19-43.: The Promise of the Spirit (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: "A Slave of Christ" (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: "A Hebrew of the Hebrews" (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: "Sold Under Sin" (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: "One Has Died for All" (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: Sinners--Yet Righteous (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: War and Peace (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: Of Faith and Love (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: Life Beyond Life (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: "The Foolishness of God" (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: Our Christian Calling (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: The New Spirit (Box 15)
    - The Theology of Paul, a twelve-article study, Crossroads, 8/3, Apr-Jun 1958, pp. 23-53.: The New Life (Box 15)
    - What is Campus Ministry. NICM Journal, Spring 1979, 7 pages. (Box 15)
    - When Are We Witnessing...And When Proselytizing?, Theology Today, XIV/3, pp. 376-383. (Box 15)
    - "Who is Heinrich Ott?": A Letter from Basel, in New Theology, No. 1, Martin E. Marty and Dean G. Peerman, eds., 1964, pp. 34-43. (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: The Mission of Jesus (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: The Manhood of the Messiah (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: Jesus and the Law (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: The Power of Forgiveness (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: The Authority of the Messiah (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: The Pearl of Great Price (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: The Fellowship of the Forgiven (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: The Basic Nature of Faith (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: "Upon This Rock" (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: The Consequences of Faith (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: The Test of Deeds (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: Works Without Faith (Box 15)
    - The Vocation of Jesus, a thirteen-article study, Crossroads, 7/2, Jan-Mar, 1957, pp. 54-81.: Who Is This Son of Man? (Box 15)
  - Jones, Robert E.
    - Mankind's Religious Nature and its Organization (Manuscript) 21 pp. (Box 15)
    - Towards Community in Theological Education (Manuscript) 20 pp., n.d. (Box 15)
  - Jones, William R.
    - Theodicy and Methodology in Black Theology: A Critique of Washington, Cone, and Cleage (Manuscript) (Box 15)
  - Kavanagh, Aidan, OSB
    - Aidan J. Kavanagh, O.S.B.: A Recognition, by Thomas H. Schattauer, ISM Symposium, April 10, 1994. (Box 16)
    - An Approach to Liturgical Style. Elements of Style, pp. 82- 105., n.d. (Box 16)
    - Christian Initiation of Adults: Rite, Worship, 48/6, pp. 318- 335., n.d. (Box 16)
    - Christliche Initiation in der Nachkonziliaren Katholischen Kirche, Liturgesches Jahrbuch, 1, 1978. (Box 16)
    - A Common Eucharistic Prayer, Leaflet of The Committee for a Common Eucharistic Prayer, Kavanagh, et al, 1975. (Box 16)
    - Convocation Address, Yale Divinity School, 1972. (Box 16)
    - Les Evenements de la Vie le Rituel Civil et les Chretiens, Concilium: Revista Internacional de Teologia, 132, 1978. Copies in French (2), German, Spanish, Italian, Dutch, and Portuguese. (Box 16)
    - Form and Function in Liturgical Worship. pp. 1-18. (Box 16)
    - Shall Never Live Forever If I Cannot Make It Through Tomorrow Morning, Yale Alumni Magazine, 39, Dec 1975, pp. 22-26. (Box 16)
    - Initiation: Baptism and Confirmation. Worship, 46/5, pp. 262-276. (Box 16)
    - Liturgie et Conscience Ecclesiale, La Maison-Dieu, 154, 1983, pp. 9-35. (Box 16)